You should leave Weechana.
Otherwise, you will be exhausted,
and your effort will go to waste.
Because I don't like you.
The others may be a better match for him
more than me.
But I will prove to you you
why your grandson picked me.
- Grandma!
- Mom!
Mom!
- Grandma?
- Mom!
Excuse me, please step back.
Give us some room.
- Are you okay?
- Oh my God! Call the ambulance.
What happened? Get a doctor.
I don't feel faint.
My knees just wobbled, that's all.
For a moment, I couldn't feel my legs.
Just get me to the couch.
Yes, Grandma.
Easy, Mom.
Thank you.
Slowly, Grandma.
Okay, thank you.
I thought I'd ask Eva
to take me to the couch.
But she said that I was strong enough
to walk to the couch myself.
And I didn't know where she went.
I tried to get to the couch myself, but...
my knees just got weak.
- Nicole, darling.
- Yeah?
- Can you take me to the other room?
- Sure.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I hope I didn't ruin your evening.
I'm sorry.
Let's go, darling.
Slowly.
Dad?
Grandma didn't tell me
that she needed to rest.
Are you accusing her of lying?
When you're around the elderly,
you should try to read their minds.
Her lips say one thing,
but her mind says another.
Grandma is the heart and soul of this house.
We need to take good care of her.
It seems like you're not used to this.
What?
I'm cool. I'm good with it.
Where were you about to go?
Eva asked me to go outside with her.
Nonsense, you should teach her some manners.
I won't pursue the matter of her
not attending to me during the party.
But I'm dismayed
that she wants you to accompany her outside
when we are still entertaining our guests.
I understand.
You need to talk to her.
I don't like people
who can't behave properly.
You feel better?
Can you stop the car? I need to talk to you.
Let's talk at your place.
I don't think so.
Domino will stay over tonight.
Before I went over to you,
your grandma said that she didn't like me.
Everyone knows about this.
I know that.
But this time,
she also said
that she prefers Nicole over me.
- Come on.
- Wee.
We've dated for two years now.
And I've tried everything.
I changed the way I dress, the way I talk,
how I conduct myself in interviews,
my dining etiquette.
I changed everything,
including how I sit, stand and lie down.
I tried to remember who your guests are
at the parties.
There must be 20-30 people to remember,
and I did.
You told me to say hi to them, and I did.
I helped out with your work. Everything.
Look at me now. It's been two years,
and your grandma still calls me
a food vendor's niece.
Eva, we talked about this.
We will fight together.
I saw your effort
and I appreciate you for that.
But if you're trying to win Grandma's heart,
your EQ needs to be better than this.
Eva.
Eva!
Don't do this, please calm down.
How much EQ is required for the situation?
Your grandma said to my face
that I should break up with you
because Nicole suits you better.
- How much EQ is required, huh?
- You need to know that Grandma is old.
And you shouldn't have
let her fall like that.
Your grandma is strong enough
to walk on a golf course.
How did her knees suddenly get weak?
- Where did she learn her acting skills from?
- Eva!
We should go.
I have work tomorrow.
Why are you home early?
What?
What happened this time?
She pretended to fall
and blamed it all on me.
Oh my goodness!
This is the perfect plot for a soap opera.
Such an ancient trick.
Are you okay?
Sure.
I love him.
I know that...
he isn't perfect.
But he's nice to me
and I want to keep fighting.
I need to star in this film.
If everything turns out well like I expected,
I will have a chance to join a film festival.
Luxury brands will book me,
and it will be a whole next step for me.
His family will then probably
be more willing to accept me.
Look, his grandma didn't focus
on the present.
She focused way back to your family origins.
No matter how good you try to be,
nothing will work
if she keeps focusing on your upbringing.
I can't choose my mother.
I can only show them
how great I am right now.
Let's go. Go, go.
You need to shower.
You'll be meeting a director tomorrow.
You need to look pretty.
Don't care about the rest.
Just focus on being pretty, okay?
Go! Go! Go!
Go take a shower.
Look at you, you're so beautiful,
as if you were an angel in your past life.
Oh my goodness! Can you do a twirl for me?
One more time, make a full turn.
Oh my goodness! Whoa!
Good night.
So there might be some changes
to the script along the way,
but there's nothing to worry about.
It's just part of the process.
Thank you.
I'm try my best.
Mai, can you ask him
about the character's personalities
that I should learn?
She'd like to know
if there are any specific details
you'd like for the character.
So she can start preparing right away.
Well, her character is a bit of a hot-head,
talks fast,
and doesn't like being misunderstood.
I want the language to feel fast and natural.
- Yeah?
- It's the language.
The character is a hot-head,
so she will need to talk fast.
- And she likes to argue.
- Got it.
Hot-headed, talks fast, likes to argue.
Got it.
Actually,
May told me
that there are some adjustments in the script.
The lead actress was born in Thailand
but she has spent time abroad for years.
Therefore, the accent is really important.
It's more than just speaking level.
He wants Eva to read the script for him
and he will make a decision later.
What?
Make a decision later? Does it mean
that I might not get the role
if my accent isn't good enough?
She wants to know if she won't get the role
if her English isn't good enough.
Well, it needs to be there.
But the director is willing
to give you more time to prepare.
And in the mean time, I want to be honest,
I might need to keep other options open
as a backup.
Language is really important.
The director will give you time
for you to practice.
But they still need to cast others
as a backup.
I got it.
Thank you for give me time.
I will try my best.
She's a good actress. She's the best one.
If I can't make them satisfied,
I will lose this role.
I know,
she is ready to get another person
to take over your role.
Where's Pun?
I'll ask him to teach me tomorrow.
I need to get the role.
Sure, okay.
[Eva Yanin]
[From street vendor's niece
to Number 1 superstar]
[Ava's fortune skyrockets]
[She enjoys a bright romance
with a young politician]
[The life of Eva Yanin:
From provincial kid to leading superstar]
[From the niece of a food vendor,
to Number 1 superstar]
[She's lucky in career and in love]
[Eva is dating a politician]
You're worried
that Eva would find out about this?
When will she know
that you're also dating me?
What for?
So she will know
that she's got herself a competitor.
[Ruam Thai Chana]
[Vote for Number 2]
[Uniting hearts, moving forward to victory]
I think a picture of me
with my arms crossing like this one
makes me unreachable and a little bit boring.
But I like this one,
with my hand in my pocket.
I look more relaxed in there.
Dad, what do you think?
Can you put my face in one of them?
Our old supporters will know
that I'm still around.
Great idea.
I want it done fast.
If we're done here,
can I have a moment with my sons?
What is your campaign plan?
I'm thinking of doing some activities
with the young voters.
They need to know that we're on their side.
Young people are more interested in politics
than before.
I want the young voters to be my stronghold.
I will organize the band contest.
We will find actors to shoot a short film.
I think it's a good idea.
Eva and Pie
should be in charge of entertainment.
I think Pie is more suitable for the job.
Pie is younger and she can
understand people in this age group.
Eva's target should be people...
who are 30 years old and older.
People in their thirties are the ones
who form the foundation of support.
They both can help with the campaign.
Okay.
Can you help me?
Wait a minute.
[Wee]
We are going home.
You're still mad at me?
I'm not mad. I know that I was wrong.
But I wasn't wrong.
I have to work out
and study my lines tomorrow.
I need to get some sleep. Talk to you later.
Okay, you should get some rest.
I love you.
Let's get home.
[Trending Shows]
Just give her some light training today,
to see how fit she is.
Do a check on her body assessment.
No need to be too hard on her, okay?
Sure, don't worry.
Don't forget to tell her
that I'll get better soon
so I can train her.
- Okay?
- Sure.
We'll talk about that later.
Here.
Wow, looks good.
You need to eat enough protein.
And you can't drink any coffee.
It decreases intestinal calcium absorption.
- Got it?
- Yes, Chef.
Whoa! Super healthy.
We have a new project to discuss later, okay?
Got it.
Jeez, the door's so heavy.
Hey.
Did you hear that?
Yeah, I did.
Should we go?
Let's go.
Follow me.
Hey.
What? Don't call me.
You need to keep it down or they'll know!
Hey!
Hey! How did you get in here?
I gave him the key, I totally forgot.
I'm sorry.
But you can't take a shower here.
This is Eva's bathroom.
That's right, and you can't
walk around naked like this.
- It's inappropriate.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Okay, I'm done.
I jogged all the way from Boat's place,
and I had sweat a lot.
I didn't know you'd be here early.
I'm really sorry.
- I forgot that...
- You can run on your way back.
So you don't need to use my bathroom.
Okay, got it.
Eva, you should get ready.
I need to talk to him.
About work.
A tutor?
That's right.
I'd like you to be her tutor,
for her English script.
Here's the plot.
A woman was born in Thailand,
but she has spent her life
in a foreign country for years.
Then she comes back to Thailand
to get revenge for her younger sister.
Seriously?
Yeah, really.
This is the accent that Eva needs to learn.
Please listen to me,
you and your friend are very well-rounded.
You two can be personal trainer,
chef and tutor.
We don't have much time,
and I'd like you to focus
on her English speaking skill.
Boat is in a cast right now.
So you need to train her and be her tutor.
When Boat comes back,
you can focus only on being her tutor.
But I can't...
No buts, please.
Please give your code.
Code?
Yeah, your rate.
My rate?
Code.
Quote!
- Quote.
- Yeah... yeah, quote.
Go ahead, man. What are you waiting for?
- But...
- You will earn more money.
After this, you can start your own business.
What about this?
I'll calculate the rate for you,
and see how much you should charge them.
In the meantime, you need to tell them,
"I need more time to think."
Stalling for time, you know?
Tell them you need more time, okay?
Okay, okay.
Let me see, how much should we charge?
What do you think?
About me being a tutor,
are you sure that I'm qualified to teach her?
Of course...
If she has totally no background in English,
shouldn't you find
a professional tutor for her?
I don't want anyone to know
that Eva needs a tutor.
What?
I know that you don't get it,
and I don't expect you to.
It's complicated in the world of celebrities.
I see.
Just trust me,
you're the most qualified
under these circumstances.
This is the script.
Here, take it.
Just have a look.
[The Black Rose]
Oh my! It's time, I need to run some errands.
I'll be back late afternoon.
Please take care of her, the script is fun.
[The Black Rose]
Eva, can I talk to you?
About?
Your conversational skills.
What about it?
I don't know about your level.
I don't know how to teach you.
You can just...
let me repeat the lines after you.
And I can imitate your accent.
Like teaching a parrot to speak?
That's rude.
No, I just want to know
what method you prefer.
Hey, I'm not a professional tutor.
And I need to tutor you
when I know nothing about it.
Eva, I can't do it.
Many people will want this chance
to work with me.
You can hire a new tutor then.
I can go back to my original position.
Okay?
Right, we will start
with your physical fitness test.
We'll start with...
jumping rope.
Why do you want to know so much
about my conversational skills?
I'm only hiring you
to help me speak English fluently.
You don't have to know everything.
It's totally fine.
There are hundreds of things
that you're better than me.
More than that.
Okay.
We're in the same boat.
If you'd like me to tutor you,
you need to tell me what you know,
and what you don't know.
I don't focus on money only.
I want you to be good at it.
Are you ready?
I don't know how.
Teach me.
[Ruam Thai Chana]
Excuse me, sir.
Our people reported
that there are many photos of you and Ginny
in the stalker's computer.
They've sent me some of them.
Who saw these pictures besides you?
Only the investigation team,
but they're working for us.
We can handle them.
Tell them to delete everything.
These photos can't be leaked.
My dad can't find out about them.
Eva can't know about them either.
Yes, sir.
Actually, I don't want to learn it
only for my work.
Many Thai people are starting
to speak English,
and those who can't,
will lose opportunities for something.
People who speak English
with a strong Thai accent
will be looked down on.
Why's that?
Actually, the westerners don't care
about dialects.
Speaking English
with Japanese, Chinese or Singaporean accents
are quite charming.
It's like when they visit our country,
they speak broken Thai
and we find them adorable.
Thai people don't find
other Thai people adorable.
It becomes an indicator of your class,
and you will be put
in a specific social status.
Nonsense.
Welcome to this world.
Before jumping rope,
you should warm up for 10 minutes,
to warm up the body and prevent injury.
Did you understand it?
Nope.
Can you speak slower?
You spoke too fast and I was startled.
Okay, okay.
Before jumping rope,
you should warm up for 10 minutes
to warm up the body and prevent injury.
Before jumping rope...
Yeah.
I need to warm up for 10 minutes.
Yes.
I didn't get the rest.
To prevent injury.
Prevent, stop it from happening.
Injury, getting hurt.
Injury. Getting hurt.
Okay, you need to widen your vocabulary.
When you're trying to say it in English,
you need to know what it means.
I want to be able to understand, speak,
respond, and have your accent.
Okay, I got you.
You need to understand about grammar.
What? Grammar?
Yeah.
I get confused even for a simple sentence.
Okay.
We need to learn for two purposes.
The first one, to learn your lines.
Focusing on understanding
the lines, the context, and the accent.
The second one,
learning to use it in conversations
in your daily life.
Let's go.
Let's start with a quick warm up.
Two minutes on the jump rope.
10 squats, slow and controlled.
And then let's finish off
with a 30-second plank.
Did you get it?
Nope.
Okay, wait.
Can you try to tell me
that you didn't understand me,
and you need me to say it again?
Again.
Is it, "tell me again"?
Alright, it's not wrong.
But... hold on.
It's not the right way to say it.
You can say...
"Come again?"
Or, "say that again."
Or you can say it informally and short, like,
"What was that?" or, "One more time."
When you don't understand what they say,
or you don't catch it,
you can ask these questions.
It's completely normal.
Okay, let's try it.
Say that again.
Not bad. One more time.
One more time.
Okay, you did great today.
Tomorrow, we'll go running.
Okay.
A run with a view.
You will tell me what the places
along our route are.
The gardens, streets, buildings or whatever.
You need to tell me in English.
That's crazy.
Are you serious?
Sorry, what was that? I don't understand.
English, please.
Crazy.
Are you crazy?
Yeah, you can say that.
Many people would say, "are you nuts?"
- Nuts?
- Yeah.
Like peanuts?
Yeah, like that.
Or, "are you out of your mind?"
You can also say, "are you kidding me?"
- Nuts?
- Yeah.
When I want to call someone
who is very crazy, what should I say?
People who are crazy?
I don't think there's a word for it.
The closest one is, "you're such an idiot."
But it's "idiot",
so it doesn't entirely mean crazy.
I think Thai words are more varied
than English words.
It won't work if you think in Thai
before you speak in English.
Hey!
Wait.
Are you trying to call me crazy?
I'm not sure. Did I say it right?
Not exactly.
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow, early morning.
I'll pick you up at home.
What?
Where is Domino?
She'll be here in 20 minutes.
Okay.
I'll keep you company until she's here.
In case, you get scared.
Okay, thanks.
Hello, Book?
Hello, Eva.
I'm Book, Ginny's manager.
Yeah?
Is everything okay?
I have something important to talk to you.
You need to know about this.
Can you come and meet me?
What's this about?
It's about Ginny and Weechana.
What do you mean?
I don't want to talk on the phone.
We should meet up.
Are you out of your mind?
Ginny's stalker tried to kill me.
And you expect me to meet you alone
without a clue of what's going on?
I'll send you something,
and you'll know what it's about.
Wee, where should we meet up in New York?
This restaurant is really nice.
I'll drop you its location.
Are we just here to eat?
Or are we going to do something else later?
Haha.
I'll take you to have some desserts later.
Ginny took her English courses in New York.
And it was the same time
that Wee was in the US.
If you think that we should meet in person,
call me.
Hey Book, I'll call you later.
I need to talk to you.
You son of a bitch!
Why did you lie to me?